[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question" : "In what children's game are participants chased by someone designated \"It\"?",
    "content" : [
        "Tag",
        "Simon Says",
        "Charades",
        "Hopscotch"
    ],
    "correct" : "Tag"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question" : "On a radio, stations are changed by using what control?",
    "content" : [
        "Tuning",
        "Volume",
        "Bass",
        "Treble"
    ],
    "correct" : "Tuning"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question" : "Which material is most dense?",
    "content" : [
        "Silver",
        "Styrofoam",
        "Butter",
        "Gold"
    ],
    "correct" : "Gold"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question" : "Which state in the United States is largest by area?",
    "content" : [
        "Alaska",
        "California",
        "Texas",
        "Hawaii"
    ],
    "correct" : "Alaska"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question" : "What is Aurora Borealis commonly known as?",
    "content" : [
        "Fairy Dust",
        "Northern Lights",
        "Book of ages",
        "a Game of Thrones main character"
    ],
    "correct" : "Northern Lights"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "An albino gorilla usually has what color fur?",
    "content": [
      "Brown",
      "Black",
      "White",
      "Golden"
    ],
    "correct": "White"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is commonly known as the \"Emerald City\" in the United States?",
    "content": [
      "Palos Verdes, CA",
      "Seattle, WA",
      "New York, NY",
      "Dallas, TX"
    ],
    "correct": "Seattle, WA"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the national emblem of Canada?",
    "content": [
      "Maple Leaf",
      "Brown Bear",
      "Maple Syrup",
      "Waffle"
    ],
    "correct": "Maple Leaf"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Oscar Awards were instituted in",
    "content": [
        "1968",
        "1929",
        "1901",
        "1965"
    ],
    "correct": "1929"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "When did Margaret Thatcher became the first female Prime Minister of Britain?",
    "content": [
        "1998",
        "1989",
        "1979",
        "1800"
    ],
    "correct": "1979"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Will I get an offer from Genesis?",
    "content": [
        "Yes",
        "Of course",
        "Sure, bro",
        "All above"
    ],
    "correct": "Sure, bro"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "When did China test their first atomic device?",
    "content": [
        "1962",
        "1963",
        "1964",
        "1965"
    ],
    "correct": "1964"
  }
]